=A Love Journal= =Episode 11=
= A Love Journal = = الحلقة 11 =
You've worked hard
لقد عملت بجد
and had a busy day.
وكان يوم حافل.
Drink some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Hello. Parking is prohibited here.
مرحبًا.  وقوف السيارات محظور هنا.
Gu Shen?
قو شين؟
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I'll lend you my car.
سوف أقرضك سيارتي.
Why do you do that?
لماذا تفعل ذلك؟
Your car broke down, didn't it?
سيارتك تعطلت ، أليس كذلك؟
You give me your car.
أعطني سيارتك.
Then what about you?
ثم ماذا عنك
Ji Chuan can drive me back.
جي تشوان يمكن أن يعيدني.
Don't bother.
لا تهتم.
I can take a taxi.
يمكنني ركوب سيارة أجرة.
Mrs. Gu.
السّيدة.  قو.
This is my obligation as your partner.
هذا هو التزامي بصفتي شريكك.
And it's so far from home.
وهو بعيد جدًا عن المنزل.
It's not a good idea to take a taxi back.
ليست فكرة جيدة أن تستعيد سيارة أجرة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
We were just thinking
كنا نفكر فقط
about how we could go back later.
حول كيف يمكننا العودة لاحقًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Take care on the way.
اعتني بنفسك على الطريق.
Wow.
رائع.
How nice of him.
كم هو لطيف منه.
He looks cold,
يبدو باردا
but he cares so much about you.
لكنه يهتم بك كثيرا.
I'm so envious.
أنا حسود جدا.
We are just a contractual couple.
نحن مجرد زوجين تعاقديين.
Fine, fine.
بخير بخير.
Contractual couple.
زوجان تعاقديان.
But,
ولكن،
you're a traffic safety propagandist.
أنت دعاية للسلامة المرورية.
You can't park the car here.
لا يمكنك ركن السيارة هنا.
Then
ثم
go with me to park the car.
اذهب معي لركن السيارة.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
(Director Office)
(مكتب المدير)
But, Mrs. Huang,
لكن ، السيدة هوانغ ،
how can we get that?
كيف نحصل على ذلك؟
We are just saleswomen,
نحن مجرد بائعات ،
not agents.
لا وكلاء.
Where to do it,
أين تفعل ذلك ،
how to do it,
كيف افعلها،
it's your business.
هذا عملك.
I only care about the results.
أنا فقط أهتم بالنتائج.
But, Mrs. Huang...
لكن ، السيدة هوانغ ...
Mrs. Huang.
السيدة هوانغ.
Leave it
اتركه
to me.
إلي
Buy it.
اشتريها.
Just a bag.
مجرد حقيبة.
It's a piece of cake.
انها قطعة من الكيك.
I'll buy the biggest one for you.
سأشتري أكبر واحد لك.
A 24-inch one.
مقاس 24 بوصة.
Okay?
تمام؟
Okay.
تمام.
Go traveling?
إذهب مسافرا؟
What a coincidence
يالها من صدفة
to see you here.
لرؤيتك هنا.
Sir.
سيد.
Coffee, please.
قهوة من فضلك.
Just a second.
لحظة.
He's paying.
يدفع.
Isn't this the assistant of my bro's wife?
أليس هذا مساعد زوجة أخي؟
Bestie.
بستي.
So,
لذا،
what are you here for?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I...
أنا...
I want to be friends with you.
أريد أن أكون صديقا لك.